AG Athena Gardner

CONTACT



PHONE

0211448275



EMAIL

athena536@hotmail.com

SUMMARY

I pride myself in being adaptable and have worked in various types of situations and working environments.

I find opportunities to learn in challenges and I see them as a way to practice my problemsolving skills. I have obtained some technical knowledge and experience communicating technical tasks within different sectors from many of my positions as well as when I took on the role of Project Liaison Officer for a web project within Manna.

KEY STRENGTHS

- Adaptable
- Problem solver
- Creative
- · Attention to detail
- Lifelong learner

URLs



https://www.linkedin.com/in/athena-gardner/



https://github.com/AthenaG536/



http://www.athena-gardner.com/

DEVELOPMENT EXPERIENCE

I love learning new languages & new techniques to utilize languages I'm familiar with. I have experience with various languages including but not limited to; Python, C#, Java, C++, SQL, HTML/CSS & JavaScript.

I also enjoy using Selenium IDE for automation testing and would love the opportunity to use this and to learn more about automation testing.

COMMUNICATION EXPERIENCE

During both my career & my studies I have done presentations & reports to a professional standard. I'm quite confident in preparing & running presentations while adjusting my terminology to my target audience and I've done these both individually & with team members.

WORK HISTORY

South Auckland Plumbing, Auckland (March 2021 - Current)

Freelancing Technical Writer (>6 months)

Manna Christian Stores, Auckland (December 2015 - July 2021)

- Information Technology Assistant (3 years, 2018 2021)
- Retail Store Manager (7 months, 2018)
- Order Picker (3 years, 2014 2018)

Supachick, Rotorua (February 2013 - October 2014)

Cashier (1 year 9 months)

During my time at Manna I was able to streamline my work, finding the most efficient ways of doing tasks freed up my time to pick up additional work.

EDUCATION

United Institute of Technology, Auckland

Bachelor of Computing Systems BCS, (2018-2021)

John Paul College, Rotorua (2008-2014)

- House Captain 2014
- NCEA Level 3
- Height Safety 2014
- Workplace Fire & Emergency Management 2014

REFERENCES

Natalia Nehring, Lecturer & Advisor Phone: + 64 9 815 4321 x 7592 Email: nnehring@unitec.ac.nz Kelly Setu, Marketing Manager & Colleague

Phone: + 64 27 5222387 Email: kelly@manna.co.nz